

PROFILE

Full Stack Software Engineer with experience producing applications to enhance business planning and operations. Highly successful at leveraging data trends and patterns.

Excited about opportunity to take the next career step in a fast-paced work environment while meeting managerial goals.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0816-096-7596

EMAIL: victorihemadu@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Reading motivational books Learning new code syntax Practicing aerobics

VICTOR IHEMADU

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDUCATION

MICHAEL OKPARA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE, UMUDIKE BSc Biochemistry – 2018

ADVENTIST SECONDARY TECHNICAL COLLEGE OWERRINTAWASSCE - 2013

TENDERFOOT INTERNATIONAL SCHOOLS FSLC – 2006

WORK EXPERIENCE

CHIGEORS INTERNATIONAL LIMITED – Data Entry Intern | June 2018 – August 2019

- Ensured the spreadsheet data was accurate, complete and followed company guidelines.
- Used time-management and prioritization skills to ensure project deadlines were met
- Processed confidential data and information according to guidelines.

NAFDAC - Laboratory Analyst Intern | April 2017 - October 2017

- Reviewed, calibrated and validated laboratory instrumentation every week.
- · Helped develop reports and analysis.
- Kept paper work and documentation for tests in order.

TRAININGS

Data Analysis - Entry Level Australia | June – August 2021
Forward Program - McKinsey & Company | May – September 2021
Database Administration – Rivers State ICT | June – September 2021
Full Stack Software Engineering – Decagon | January 2022 – Present

SKILLS

